notefish.com 2009-04-02

# Privacy Policy - Notefish

Notefish respects your privacy. This document lays out our privacy policy. We hope that this privacy policy will help you to make an informed choice about using our services. 

#### Policy Scope

This policy covers how Notefish treats the information it may collect during your interaction with the Notefish website or your use of the Notefish service. This policy does not cover the websites Notefish does not control including all websites that serve as sources for your Notefish pages. 

#### Information Collection and Use

Notefish may collect the following information about you: 

Registration information
     When you sign up for the Notefish service we ask you to provide your name, your e-mail address, which is used as your user name, and your password. This registration information is necessary to provide the service to you. 
Notefish pages
     Notefish stores and processes all your Notefish data including pages, notes, links to your note sources, creation and modification dates, images and so on. Storing this data is an essential part of providing the service to you. 
Cookies
     In order to provide services to you, we require cookies to be enabled in your browser. Cookies are small character strings we send to your browser to uniquely identify it. This requirement a standard practice used by many online services. The browsers we support have cookies enabled by default. 
Server logs
     Our equipment automatically records the information your browser sends to us when you visit the Notefish website or use the Notefish service. The information may include a page name, a page URL, your IP address, visit time, browser type, browser language, search string, and the cookies. We may use this information to research web site and service usage patterns, and eventually improve the service. 
User Communication
     When you use a feedback form on the Notefish website, we may record your user name along with your comments. When you send us an e-mail, we may store it for further communication with you, or for future reference. 

Notefish only uses personal information for the following purposes: 

  * Providing service to our users
  * Research and analysis aimed to improve, protect, and maintain the services as well as to develop new services 
  * Provide targeted advertising to our users via third parties (see the section 'Information Sharing') 

All information Notefish collects and processes is stored in the USA at equipment of a U.S. hosting provider company. 

#### Information Sharing

Notefish will not share information about you with individuals or organizations except under the following circumstances: 

  * We have your permission
  * We have reasonable belief that sharing information is necessary to satisfy a law, regulation, legal process or enforcible governmental request; to enforce Terms of Use; to protect against harm to Notefish, Notefish users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
  * We may share the contents of your Notefish pages with advertisement provider companies to deliver targeted advertisement to you. We do not share your e-mail, your name, or any other information that could potentially identify you unless this information is a part of your Notefish page. We only partner with advertisement providers who claim their advertisement matching is completely automated and does not involve human personnel. 
  * We may share your visit information that may include a page name, a page URL, your IP address, visit time, browser type, browser language, browser version, browser plugin versions (such as Macromedia Flash version), OS type, OS version, internet connection speed, screen resolution with 3rd party analysis tools such as Google Analytics to research web service usage patterns. We do not share your name or contents of your pages with such tools. 

#### Information Security

All personal information is stored at facilities and equipment provided a by U.S. based hosting company who was able to demonstrate that reasonable security measures are taken to prevent unauthorized information disclosure or loss. 

#### Policy Changes

From time to time we may change this policy and advise you to review it so that you can make an informed decision about using the Notefish service. 

#### Feedback

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy please contact us at [privacy@notefish.com](mailto:privacy@notefish.com)

* * *

© 2006 Notefish
